<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Jacob Robinson</title>
    <link>https://jacrobin.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Jacob Robinson</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 15:36:58 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jacrobin.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>September Update</title>
      <link>https://jacrobin.github.io/posts/september-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 15:36:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jacrobin.github.io/posts/september-update/</guid>
      <description>I Messed Up Hey all, so much for a post every month ¯\_(ツ)_/¯. No seriously, August was a little rough for me so I did slack. I spent a lot of time applying to jobs this month. The daily barrage of rejection emails and subsequent daily applications had really put me into a funk. I stopped keeping track a little after graduating, but I easily submitted at least 10 a week minimum, most weeks felt like I did at least 30.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Day Build (ODB) #1: Temperature &amp; Humidity Sensor Part: i</title>
      <link>https://jacrobin.github.io/posts/one-day-build-temp-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 14:15:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jacrobin.github.io/posts/one-day-build-temp-i/</guid>
      <description>Intro: This is a new thing I want to start doing where I try to build something at least once a month, and within a day (ideally). To kick things off I wanted to test, and build, a simple arduino powered temperature and humidity sensor. This overall took about three hours including testing of planning, sensors, wiring, testing, and coding.
Build Overview: The build needed to meet two criteria:
 Read both humidity and temperature reliably Be able to connect to a RaspberryPi later (Part: ii)  To meet these criteria an Arduino was used.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Failure</title>
      <link>https://jacrobin.github.io/posts/failure/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 20:56:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jacrobin.github.io/posts/failure/</guid>
      <description>Apollo 1 Command module, after the fire that killed Gus Grissom, Edward White II, and Roger Chaffee.
I’ve been thinking about failure a lot lately. Not only my failures but the concept of failure in general. In a time where everyone seems divided in some capacity, failure is still a rudimentary universal experience everyone can relate to. From leadership, avionics, innovation, friendships, and academia. All failure at their point of perception feel earth-shattering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The State of the Home Lab 2023</title>
      <link>https://jacrobin.github.io/posts/the-state-of-the-home-lab-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 13:28:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jacrobin.github.io/posts/the-state-of-the-home-lab-2023/</guid>
      <description>Upgrading My Workflow For those who don&amp;rsquo;t know me, I love tinkering with hardware and software. I am also the type of person who will do something a hundred times before deciding on the best strategy for dealing with a given problem. I only just finished my undergraduate studies for cybersecurity, so for the last year or so my home lab was the last thing I was allocating time to. However, with all my new found free-time, I wanted something to work on in the midst of frantically applying for jobs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
