<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Jacob Robinson</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Jacob Robinson</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 19:17:33 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Whats Important</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-important/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 19:17:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-important/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>End of Summer Update</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/end_of_summer_update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 19:02:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/end_of_summer_update/</guid>
      <description>Hello all!
I&amp;rsquo;ve been fairly quiet recently, mainly because I moved across the country and I started my new job in the spring. Both have been an experience to say the least. Obviously this has been in a transitional period of my life and for the first time I am truly &amp;lsquo;adult-ing&amp;rsquo;.
Another challenge is I don&amp;rsquo;t have any of my gear. Its going to be a while until I get all my equipment to my new location.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OSINT Challenge - Feb 7th Iraq Airstrike</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/osint-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 21:04:34 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/osint-challenge/</guid>
      <description>On February 7th, 2024 at 9:30 PM in Baghdad, Iraq the U.S military conducted an air strike on a single vehicle that contained a senior leader of Kata’ib Hezbollah who USCENTCOM says both planned and took part in attacks of U.S forces in the region. At this time USCENTCOM says that other than the passengers there are no other fatalities.
For the past two days I have been trying to learn and practice practical OSINT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lets go 2024!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/hello_2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 09:51:54 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/hello_2024/</guid>
      <description>LETS GO 2024 Very excited for what is to come this year. After graduating in June with my B.S in cyber security I am poised to get employed sometime this year. While the news about the tech sector is doom and gloom, I do have some opportunities in the works. I have a conditional offer with the government, but I havn&amp;rsquo;t well, yet met the conditions (I guess), but in time everything should be good to go.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
