<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Jacob Robinson</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Jacob Robinson</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 21:26:40 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>One Year Anniversary Reflections</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/one_year_reflectoins/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 21:26:40 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/one_year_reflectoins/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;May 1st of this year was the anniversary of my first real job after getting my degree. A year ago I had trepidation in taking the step towards my current role. The process was tedious, to the point I almost quit along the way. I knew I would be making sacrifices that I would regret later. But I knew I would be doing something I would love, and be apart of something bigger than myself.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Well</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/well/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 22:16:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/well/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So…yeah…things are kinda interesting in America right now. As a public servant, job security is turbulent to say the least. For the last few weeks I have been preparing for several scenarios when certain thresholds are met. My current goal is to make it at least to the two year mark at my current employer and then relocate to Washington if something pans out. However I must be ready for several scenarios where I may have to do that post haste.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/hello_2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 15:07:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/hello_2025/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Well it is that time again&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2024 was a blur for myself personally and professionally. I grew a lot in some areas and stagnated in others. 2025 has kicked off a bit of a bumpy start, but I am confident this year will be even better than the last. I am already four months away from the first year anniversary of my new job, and I am really enjoying it!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whats Important</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-important/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 19:17:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-important/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
