<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Jacob Robinson</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jacob Robinson</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 19:17:33 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Whats Important</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-important/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 19:17:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-important/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>End of Summer Update</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/end_of_summer_update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 19:02:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/end_of_summer_update/</guid>
      <description>Hello all!
I&amp;rsquo;ve been fairly quiet recently, mainly because I moved across the country and I started my new job in the spring. Both have been an experience to say the least. Obviously this has been in a transitional period of my life and for the first time I am truly &amp;lsquo;adult-ing&amp;rsquo;.
Another challenge is I don&amp;rsquo;t have any of my gear. Its going to be a while until I get all my equipment to my new location.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 11:45:57 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/home/</guid>
      <description>Who am I? My name is Jacob. I am a aspiring cyber security practitioner, professional nerd, and part time poet. My posts range in topics, but normally deal with technology or cyber security in some fashion.
What do I want to do? Currently I am pursing a path towards public sector work in cyber security. It seems like the best choice for myself with the current macro economic conditions and tech job market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OSINT Challenge - Feb 7th Iraq Airstrike</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/osint-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 21:04:34 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/osint-challenge/</guid>
      <description>On February 7th, 2024 at 9:30 PM in Baghdad, Iraq the U.S military conducted an air strike on a single vehicle that contained a senior leader of Kata’ib Hezbollah who USCENTCOM says both planned and took part in attacks of U.S forces in the region. At this time USCENTCOM says that other than the passengers there are no other fatalities.
For the past two days I have been trying to learn and practice practical OSINT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lets go 2024!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/hello_2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 09:51:54 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/hello_2024/</guid>
      <description>LETS GO 2024 Very excited for what is to come this year. After graduating in June with my B.S in cyber security I am poised to get employed sometime this year. While the news about the tech sector is doom and gloom, I do have some opportunities in the works. I have a conditional offer with the government, but I havn&amp;rsquo;t well, yet met the conditions (I guess), but in time everything should be good to go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ask Iwata Review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2023-post/ask-iwata-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 14:50:36 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2023-post/ask-iwata-review/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR I recently finished reading this book, and I really enjoyed it. If you don&amp;rsquo;t know who the late Satoru Iwata is he is a Japanese business man who worked his way up to president of HAL, eventually the president of Nintendo. He tragically passed away in July of 2015 at the age of 55, but his impact and influence on Nintendo and their customers will tell the test of time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>September Update</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2023-post/september-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 15:36:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2023-post/september-update/</guid>
      <description>I Messed Up Hey all, so much for a post every month ¯\_(ツ)_/¯. No seriously, August was a little rough for me so I did slack. I spent a lot of time applying to jobs this month. The daily barrage of rejection emails and subsequent daily applications had really put me into a funk. I stopped keeping track a little after graduating, but I easily submitted at least 10 a week minimum, most weeks felt like I did at least 30.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Day Build (ODB) #1: Temperature &amp; Humidity Sensor Part: i</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2023-post/one-day-build-temp-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 14:15:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2023-post/one-day-build-temp-i/</guid>
      <description>Intro: This is a new thing I want to start doing where I try to build something at least once a month, and within a day (ideally). To kick things off I wanted to test, and build, a simple arduino powered temperature and humidity sensor. This overall took about three hours including testing of planning, sensors, wiring, testing, and coding.
Build Overview: The build needed to meet two criteria:
Read both humidity and temperature reliably Be able to connect to a RaspberryPi later (Part: ii) To meet these criteria an Arduino was used.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Failure</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2023-post/failure/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 20:56:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2023-post/failure/</guid>
      <description>Apollo 1 Command module, after the fire that killed Gus Grissom, Edward White II, and Roger Chaffee.
I’ve been thinking about failure a lot lately. Not only my failures but the concept of failure in general. In a time where everyone seems divided in some capacity, failure is still a rudimentary universal experience everyone can relate to. From leadership, avionics, innovation, friendships, and academia. All failure at their point of perception feel earth-shattering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The State of the Home Lab 2023</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2023-post/the-state-of-the-home-lab-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 13:28:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2023-post/the-state-of-the-home-lab-2023/</guid>
      <description>Upgrading My Workflow For those who don&amp;rsquo;t know me, I love tinkering with hardware and software. I am also the type of person who will do something a hundred times before deciding on the best strategy for dealing with a given problem. I only just finished my undergraduate studies for cybersecurity, so for the last year or so my home lab was the last thing I was allocating time to. However, with all my new found free-time, I wanted something to work on in the midst of frantically applying for jobs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, my name is Jacob I was originally born in Florida, but currently reside in the Pacific Northwest. I am an cybersecurity professional. I hold a B.S in cybersecurity from Western Washington University (NSA CAE-D Certified) and have a range of interests in the industry.
I interned at Twilio in the summer of 2022, and worked as a operational resilience analyst. My work focused on control auditing, process workflow improvements, and secure software life cycle recommendations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
