<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Jacob Robinson</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jacob Robinson</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 15:07:52 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hello 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/hello_2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 15:07:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/hello_2025/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Well it is that time again&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2024 was a blur for myself personally and professionally. I grew a lot in some areas and stagnated in others. 2025 has kicked off a bit of a bumpy start, but I am confident this year will be even better than the last. I am already four months away from the first year anniversary of my new job, and I am really enjoying it!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>End of Summer Update</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024-post/end_of_summer_update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 19:02:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024-post/end_of_summer_update/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello all!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been fairly quiet recently, mainly because I moved across the country and I started my new job in the spring. Both have been an experience to say the least. Obviously this has been a transitional period of my life and for the first time I am truly &amp;lsquo;adult-ing&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another challenge is I don&amp;rsquo;t have any of my gear. Its going to be a while until I get all my equipment to my new location. This married with my lack of free time has constrained exactly what projects I am going to pursue in the near future. I have some ideas, but a lot of my time in the next quarter or so is slated for education in the form of SANS classes or certificates/degrees. I would like to get to a place that I build foundational skills in something else in the IT/OT/cybersecurity space than I am currently doing, and have something of a side hustle in the coming years. But I acknowledge that this would mean the potential of having effectively two full time jobs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 11:45:57 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/home/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;who-am-i&#34;&gt;Who am I?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My name is Jacob. I am a aspiring cyber security practitioner, professional nerd, and part time poet. My &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/posts&#34;&gt;posts&lt;/a&gt; range in topics, but normally deal with technology or cyber security in some fashion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/IMG_1523.png#center&#34; alt=&#34;a&#34;  /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-do-i-want-to-do&#34;&gt;What do I want to do?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Currently I am pursing a path towards public sector work in cyber security. It seems like the best choice for myself with the current macro economic conditions and tech job market. Eventually I&amp;rsquo;d like to try roles in the cyber intelligence domain or research. That said I am still actively applying to roles in the private sector in almost every domain in cyber. Do you have shovels? I have hands.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OSINT Challenge - Feb 7th Iraq Airstrike</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024-post/osint-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 21:04:34 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024-post/osint-challenge/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On February 7th, 2024 at 9:30 PM in Baghdad, Iraq the U.S military conducted an air strike on a single vehicle that contained a senior leader of Kata’ib Hezbollah who &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.centcom.mil/MEDIA/PRESS-RELEASES/Press-Release-View/Article/3669808/uscentcom-conducts-strike-killing-kataib-hezbollah-senior-leader/&#34;&gt;USCENTCOM&lt;/a&gt; says both planned and took part in attacks of U.S forces in the region. At this time USCENTCOM says that other than the passengers there are no other fatalities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the past two days I have been trying to learn and practice practical OSINT. I thought about debunking some misinformation on twitter, or geolocating a friend in a picture. But after seeing the anger in Iraq because of the strike I thought that there might be enough info on social media for me to work with in narrowing down the location. My goal was simple, use as little official release info to get the exact coordinates of the strike using only public resources and reporting. I started by collecting photos and stills from videos both shortly after the airstrike, and later on during clean up efforts when more people would be filming. But first I needed to get down to the rough area of the strike. Looking through media reports and &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/i/status/1755301942501195958&#34;&gt;X posts&lt;/a&gt; I saw several mentions of &lt;code&gt;Al Mashtal area&lt;/code&gt;and &lt;code&gt; Al Mashtal neighborhood, eastern Baghdad, Iraq&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lets go 2024!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024-post/hello_2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 09:51:54 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024-post/hello_2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/2024/eva-title.png#center&#34; alt=&#34;a&#34;  /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;lets-go-2024&#34;&gt;LETS GO 2024&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Very excited for what is to come this year. After graduating in June with my B.S in cyber security I am poised to get employed sometime this year. While the news about the tech sector is doom and gloom, I do have some opportunities in the works. I have a conditional offer with the government, but I havn&amp;rsquo;t well, yet met the conditions (I guess), but in time everything should be good to go. In the mean time (and in case it doesn&amp;rsquo;t work out with uncle sam) I am still looking for employment in the private sector. And after +500-ish applications since May, and about 4 interviews it definitely seems challenging out here right now, but I am confident it will all work out. Worst case its back to retail and cyber volunteering or an apprenticeship.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ask Iwata Review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2023-post/ask-iwata-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 14:50:36 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2023-post/ask-iwata-review/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;tldr&#34;&gt;TL;DR&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I recently finished reading this book, and I really enjoyed it. If you don&amp;rsquo;t know who the late Satoru Iwata is he is a Japanese business man who worked his way up to president of HAL, eventually the president of Nintendo. He tragically passed away in July of 2015 at the age of 55, but his impact and influence on Nintendo and their customers will tell the test of time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>September Update</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2023-post/september-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 15:36:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2023-post/september-update/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;i-messed-up&#34;&gt;I Messed Up&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hey all, so much for a post every month &lt;code&gt;¯\_(ツ)_/¯&lt;/code&gt;. No seriously, August was a little rough for me so I did slack. I spent a lot of time applying to jobs this month. The daily barrage of rejection emails and subsequent daily applications had really put me into a funk. I stopped keeping track a little after graduating, but I easily submitted at least 10 a week minimum, most weeks felt like I did at least 30. Since June I think I am in the high 300 applications range. Any who, the good-news is I am walking into September with a few prospects, to you know, make a living.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Day Build (ODB) #1: Temperature &amp; Humidity Sensor Part: i</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2023-post/one-day-build-temp-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 14:15:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2023-post/one-day-build-temp-i/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro:&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a new thing I want to start doing where I try to build something at least once a month, and within a day (ideally). To kick things off I wanted to test, and build, a simple arduino powered temperature and humidity sensor. This overall took about three hours including testing of planning, sensors, wiring, testing, and coding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;build-overview&#34;&gt;Build Overview:&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The build needed to meet two criteria:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Read both humidity and temperature reliably&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be able to connect to a RaspberryPi later (Part: ii)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To meet these criteria an Arduino was used. While a RaspberryPi alone could have been used, the added complexity of separate system communication had more appeal.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Failure</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2023-post/failure/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 20:56:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2023-post/failure/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/372px-Apollo_1%27s_Command_Module_-_GPN-2003-00057.jpeg#center&#34; alt=&#34;a&#34;  /&gt;

&lt;sup&gt;Apollo 1 Command module, after the fire that killed Gus Grissom, Edward White II, and Roger Chaffee.&lt;sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve been thinking about failure a lot lately. Not only my failures but the concept of failure in general. In a time where everyone seems divided in some capacity, failure is still a rudimentary universal experience everyone can relate to. From leadership, avionics, innovation, friendships, and academia. All failure at their point of perception feel earth-shattering.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The State of the Home Lab 2023</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2023-post/the-state-of-the-home-lab-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 13:28:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2023-post/the-state-of-the-home-lab-2023/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;upgrading-my-workflow&#34;&gt;Upgrading My Workflow&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those who don&amp;rsquo;t know me, I love tinkering with hardware and software. I am also the type of person who will do something a hundred times before deciding on the best strategy for dealing with a given problem. I only just finished my undergraduate studies for cybersecurity, so for the last year or so my home lab was the last thing I was allocating time to. However, with all my new found free-time, I wanted something to work on in the midst of frantically applying for jobs. First, though I wanted a platform in place before working on projects, hence Home Lab 3.0.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/pfp.png#center&#34; alt=&#34;a&#34;  /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;hi-my-name-is-jacob&#34;&gt;Hi, my name is Jacob&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was originally born in Florida, but currently reside in the  Pacific Northwest. I am an cybersecurity professional. I hold a B.S in cybersecurity from Western Washington University (NSA CAE-D Certified) and have a range of interests in the industry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I interned at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.twilio.com/en-us&#34;&gt;Twilio&lt;/a&gt; in the summer of 2022, and worked as a operational resilience analyst. My work focused on control auditing, process workflow improvements, and secure software life cycle recommendations. Additionally, I have experience with &lt;a href=&#34;https://pisces-intl.org/&#34;&gt;PISCES&lt;/a&gt; as a network security analyst during my course work at WWU.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
